hagerty.com 2019-03-15

# Hagerty.com Privacy Policy

## Summary of this Privacy Policy

At Hagerty, we are committed to respecting your privacy. For this reason, we want to be upfront with you in terms of letting you know what information we may collect and how we might use it.

This website may be co-branded with a Hagerty affiliate or partner. Although Hagerty remains the sole owner of the information collected on this site, non-public personal information may be shared with Hagerty affiliates or partners to service or complete requested transactions. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Hagerty collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

This Privacy Policy applies to any Hagerty business transaction. This Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include Hagerty services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies and offer other relevant ads.

### In Plain English

We respect your privacy and your car skills. This page explains how we treat your information.

## Insurance Products and Services

If you are a Hagerty insurance client or a potential insurance client, please refer to our Insurance Privacy policy for specific privacy rights and information. The Insurance Privacy Policy is intended to be read in conjunction with this policy, but it is specifically designed to address privacy issues surrounding Hagerty’s insurance products.

### In Plain English

If you have an insurance policy through us you clearly have good taste, but feel free to check out our Insurance Client Privacy Policy for more information.

## International Data Transfers, EU-US Privacy Shield

Hagerty participates in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework (“Privacy Shield”), and has self-certified with the Department of Commerce that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. Hagerty is committed to applying the Privacy Shield Principles to all personal information received from countries in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) in reliance on the Privacy Shield. To learn more about the Privacy Shield, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s [Privacy Shield Information](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). To see how Hagerty treats personal information from the EEA, please see our Privacy Shield Notice. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

## The Information We Collect and How We Use It

### Automatically Gathered Information:

We can gather some information automatically from our website through the use of cookies or the use of third-party service providers. We also collect information we receive from you during any online registrations or insurance applications and when you complete other forms.

Automatically gathered information includes: Your browser type and language, and operating system, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the times that you visit our website, information about areas of our website you visited, the sites you visited immediately before and after visiting our website, web pages and advertisements you view and links you click within our website, unique identifiers when using a mobile device, including mobile device identification numbers, information that can identify the physical location of your mobile device in accordance with applicable law and industry guidelines and best practices, information about your interaction with email messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to non-public personal information. We will obtain your permission before we identify the physical location of your device and before we engage in any continuous tracking of your device’s location.

### In Plain English

#### Automatically Gathered Information:

We like smooth-running cars and websites. To keep this website running smoothly we gather information that tells us about you about how you’re accessing our website. We own the boring technical data. This information allows us to customize your experience. 

### Cookies:

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies are used on our site to enhance and simplify the user’s visit. We use cookies to gather information on your preferences to provide you with a more custom experience. For instance, we send a cookie whenever an application has been started and can help us re-market to you through banner advertisements. This allows the user to access his or her application upon future visits. If a user rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our website but will not have access to these enhancements. For more information on Hagerty’s use of cookies, please see our International Cookie Statement.

### Website Analytics:

We have enabled Google and Adobe Analytics Advertising to assist us with collecting various pieces of demographic information. Specifically, we have enabled geographic and general website movement pattern features. You can opt out of these analytics features that we use by utilizing [Adobe’s](https://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html) or [Google's](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) currently available opt-outs.

### Third Parties:

We may also collect information from third-party service providers, consumer reports, credit based consumer reports, or mobile devices. Any information we collect about you may be combined and used to help us tailor our communications to you and may be shared with third parties consistent with this Privacy Policy. This information may also be used to determine your eligibility for an insurance policy.

### Information Directly from You:

We may gather other information directly from you. While you do not have to provide any information to visit our website, we may request information from you to better serve you when you register or apply for certain services. Information we may collect directly from you includes contact information such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, payment information, user name, password, password-reminder questions and answers, age and date of birth, social security number, demographic information, information for a public profile such as interests, a profile photograph, descriptive information that you provide, Facebook page, Twitter profile, communication preferences, search queries, and any other information that may help us to provide customized content or advertising to you. Demographic information is information that does not reveal your specific identity.

### In Plain English

#### Information Directly from You:

You can provide us with information about you, such as your name, email address, phone number, etc. It is completely up to you what information you like to voluntarily provide to us.

## Access and Correction of Personal Information

You have the right to access and correct the personal information that we have collected from or about you. To do so, simply contact Hagerty’s customer service department. This does not apply to legally privileged information, work product, or information involved in an ongoing investigation. If you'd like to correct information that you provided to us, our representative will make the appropriate adjustments to Hagerty’s records. If you wish to correct personal information provided to Hagerty by a third party (such as a credit rating agency) the representative will provide you with the applicable third party's contact information.

### In Plain English

If you want to update or see any information that we have about you, just let us know. But we may not be able to share information involved in an ongoing investigation.

## Co-Browsing Assistance

To assist you, Hagerty may provide a co-browsing service that allows Hagerty employees to view only your Hagerty window with you. Hagerty employees will not be able to view any other webpages from your browser. You will be required to acknowledge and agree to this assistance before Hagerty employees can use this service to help you. Hagerty will endeavor to keep all private and confidential information secure to the extent possible. Hagerty will not be able to control any actions on your browser. The co-browsing product will only allow Hagerty to only view, not operate, the client’s browser. Any payment information, social security numbers, or other sensitive personal information will not be viewable by Hagerty at this stage.

### In Plain English

A helping hand is always nice, even if you’re just changing a flat. Hagerty offers a tool that allows our agents to see what you see online and walk you through any problems. We cannot see any of your personal or payment information.

## Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Hagerty is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, the privacy statements and practices of those websites govern their use of your information. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects non-public personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### In Plain English

If you go to another website from ours they may collect information from you. Our privacy policy does not apply to those websites. Their garage, their rules.

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes and for permission-based e-mail promotions and information. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site, as well as summarizing the results of all respondents and reporting on industry statistics, trends, and group opinions.

### In Plain English

Sometimes we have a survey or contest. These are 100% voluntary. Any information collected from a survey or contest will only be used to make our website or products better and to contact any winners.

## Affiliate Programs

An affiliate is a Hagerty owned company. For example, Hagerty DriveShare is an affiliate of Hagerty Insurance Agency, LLC. If you elect to sign up for an affiliate program, we will collect some information, such as contact information and location, from you. This information is used only for conducting business with the affiliate and is not shared with outside parties.

### In Plain English

We own some other companies and these are called “affiliates.” If you purchase something from an affiliate of ours, we will need to collect some information. That information stays between us and our affiliate and is not shared with anybody else.

## Use of Your Information

First and foremost, we use the information we collect from you to determine whether we can underwrite an insurance policy once you submit an application and to issue the policy if we accept your application. We will also use your information to assists us in settling any insurance claims you may have with us.

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and within the Hagerty family of companies. This is not linked to any non-public personal information that can identify any individual person.

### In Plain English

We use your information to issue an insurance policy or settle a claim to protect your sweet ride. We also use your information to send membership communications including emails, magazines, and invitations.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We do not sell or rent any non-public personal information about you to any third party. However, there are certain circumstances in which your non-public personal information may be disclosed. We may be forced to disclose information to the government or authorities to comply with applicable law. We may also disclose non-public personal information about you in response to a judicial or administrative order in a criminal, civil, or administrative proceeding or investigation.

We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When a user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use non-public personal information except for the purpose of providing these services. We may also share policy information with a licensed agent or broker who referred your to us.

We may also voluntarily disclose such information if we, in our sole discretion, believe it to be necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is either illegal or tortious, or may expose us to legal liability. Non-public personal information may be shared with Hagerty affiliates or partners to service or complete requested transactions. Additionally, regardless of the security measures that we take, your non-public personal information may be disclosed inadvertently if a third party acts intentionally to intercept it. If we have a need to share your information for any new or other reason outside of this current policy, we will ask your permission.

We may use an outside shipping company to ship policies, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use non-public personal information for any secondary purposes.

If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes or we otherwise transfer assets relating to our business or this website to a third party, such as by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy proceeding or otherwise, we may transfer or sell your personal information to the new owner. In such a case, unless permitted otherwise by applicable law, your information would remain subject to the promises made in the applicable privacy policy unless you agree differently.

### In Plain English

Let’s be clear: We do not sell or rent any of your personal information to anybody, ever. We will disclose personal information: 

  * If we are required to by a court subpoena
  * If law enforcement requires it to investigate or stop a crime
  * To hold up our end of our business transaction with you. For example, we will share some information with a flatbed tow company for our roadside service
  * To process a credit card transaction
  * To ship products or documents to you
  * If the ownership of Hagerty ever changes, we will transfer your information to the new owner and the same protection will apply unless a law says otherwise

If we want to share it for some other reason, we’ll get your permission first!

## Security

Hagerty uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your non-public personal information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers (SSL). We have implemented security measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information we collect or receive from you. For example, when you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using SSL technology. We will use personally identifiable information, if any, that we collect and receive from you in ways only for the reason we collected it and consistent with this Policy. We will take steps to ensure that all personally identifiable information collected, processed, and/or stored is protected from destruction, corruption, or use in a manner inconsistent with the purpose for which we received it. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet but we will endeavor to keep your private information secure.

### In Plain English

We take appropriate steps consistent with the industry to protect your information. We use current technology and tools to keep your information safe. But nothing is perfect so please be careful and use strong passwords.

## Public Forums

This site may make forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### In Plain English

Our website has a group forum for car people to talk shop. Just remember that anything you post becomes public.

## Our Policies Concerning Children

Hagerty does not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years old without parental consent. In the event we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected information from children under age 13 without parental consent, we will take measures to remove such information from our servers. If you believe that we might have any personal information from a child aged under 13, please contact us at [800-922-4050](tel:800-922-4050) or [privacy@hagerty.com](mailto:privacy@hagerty.com).

### In Plain English

We don’t plan on collecting information from children under 13 without parental consent. If we do accidentally receive this information, we will delete it. If you think we have received a child’s information, please contact us at [800-922-4050](tel:800-922-4050) or [privacy@hagerty.com](mailto:privacy@hagerty.com).

## Your California Privacy Rights

We only share personal information with third parties for to market directly to you if you either specifically opt-in, or have the opportunity to opt-out and elect not to opt-out of that sharing.

Like many other websites and online services, we do not currently alter our practices when we receive Do Not Track signals as there is no consensus among industry participants as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. To find out more about "Do Not Track," you may wish to contact us at [privacy@hagerty.com](mailto:privacy@hagerty.com).

### In Plain English

We don’t want to be backseat drivers when it comes to your privacy. So we will only share information with a third party to market directly to you if you decide that you want them to.

If we receive a “do not track” signal from your internet browser we don’t currently change anything because professionals and lawmakers have not agreed on what can and should be done. Feel free to talk to us about “do not track” signals at [privacy@hagerty.com](mailto:privacy@hagerty.com).

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time as we continue to evaluate this policy against new technologies, regulations, and business practices. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

### In Plain English

This Privacy Policy isn’t all original. We have to modify it from time to time with aftermarket parts to keep up with the times. We will make big changes easy to find.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Hagerty, simply contact us at [800-922-4050](tel:800-922-4050) or [privacy@hagerty.com](mailto:privacy@hagerty.com).

### In Plain English

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Hagerty, simply contact us at [800-922-4050](tel:800-922-4050) or [privacy@hagerty.com](mailto:privacy@hagerty.com).
